{
    "id": "6a6a5e9a4d484ce09c2ac767126a4a6a",
    "title": "Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She is younger than ……………………..",
            "description": "Object pronouns are preferred after as and than. Subject pronouns are unusual unless they are accompanied by verbs. ",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "me",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8d51c153f0324054aea95784541bab65"
        },
        {
            "question": "She works hard to support ……………………… family.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "her",
                "hers",
                "her's"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "48b66e0fd7d44356be07436221a6652d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I never realized that …………………….. was making a mistake.",
            "description": "A pronoun used as the subject of a verb should be in its subject form. ",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "me"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "da7a62b9dc754e148701140b1d7a0037"
        },
        {
            "question": "She asked ……………………… what …………………… wanted.",
            "description": "A pronoun used as the verb should be in its object form. Here him is the object of the verb asked and he is the subject of the verb wanted. ",
            "answers": [
                "he, him",
                "him, he",
                "him, him"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ad54ba5daaf94ba6bd783f912f40d297"
        },
        {
            "question": "The young boy is eager to please ………………………. employer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "him",
                "he",
                "his"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f5d11ff9cab64120a764e0920240916f"
        },
        {
            "question": "What she said made no sense to ……………………..",
            "description": "A pronoun used as the object of a preposition should be in its object form. ",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "me",
                "mine"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "666fc9c4e16b4844bed06ee016e99d6f"
        },
        {
            "question": "They took ………………………… to the doctor.",
            "description": "Here him is the object of the verb took. ",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "him",
                "his"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c7708e429bbb472c827dccdbd73efbca"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have known ……………………….. for a long time.",
            "description": "They is a subject pronoun and them is an object pronoun. A pronoun used as the object of a verb should be in its object form. ",
            "answers": [
                "they",
                "them"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "04368af620004d019bf42d830f0f825a"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is my bag. Which one is ………………………….?",
            "description": "Yours is the possessive form of you. ",
            "answers": [
                "your",
                "yours"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ef102a29d5dc464db124abcf75b71c58"
        },
        {
            "question": "That red car is ………………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "me",
                "my",
                "mine"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d34f31ef9c084ef789c2e1cb0e03a9f3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Whose bag is this? It is …………………………",
            "description": "Her is an object pronoun hers is its possessive form.",
            "answers": [
                "her",
                "hers"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c1bcb0f90c134974977fc9eaa30ccdad"
        },
        {
            "question": "He made …………………….. wait for hours.",
            "description": "Me is the object form of the pronoun I. ",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "me",
                "my"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "93ba7f0d0fdc48ee96e8bb6bb7fbbc13"
        }
    ]
}